How often have we only been 8 days away
where the odds of a rate hike versus a
pause or a rate cut, whatever, is a coin
flip? Usually by this point, there's an
80 to 90% observation as to what's going
to happen.
So, what this means is that the stakes
are higher because we're getting closer
to and closer to the event without any
resolution. We don't know what's going
to happen. When this happens, when we
get to higher levels of uncertainty, it
leads to more violent market reactions
in both directions. But, when we're only
about a week away
and it's still a coin flip, it means
whatever the resolution is will likely
lead to a more violent impact on the
markets than they otherwise would have,
which is typical, which is a hallmark of
what happens when you have increased
uncertainty occurring.